

Mohsen Shabanian

Full Stack Web Developer

Full Stack Web Developer with 5+ years of experience in designing and developing user interfaces, testing, debugging, training staff, and working closely with clients. Working as a website and webapplication Developer with different frameworks like .Net(C#) and Laravel(PHP) framework. knowing tools like Git, SQL-Server, and MySQL. Also, I have a little experience with C/C++, Python, MongoDB, and ReactJs.

Ramsar, Iran

n linkedin.com/in/mohsen-shabanian-8869b478

github.com/mohsen12999

+989113923310

www.MohsenShabanian.com

twitter.com/mohsen1299

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer Self-employed (freelancer)

11/2018 – Present

Ramsar

Develop website and web-application

- Admin Page with reporting data in tables and graphs.
- Multiple admin user roles with different page and access.
- Develop SMS authentication and send, receive and process code via messages.

Co-Founder and Developer APDR co.

11/2017 – 11/2018

Ramsar

CEO

- Project Management.
- Problem-Solving.
- Decision-Making.
- Teamwork & Collaboration.

Full Stack Web Developer Amard co.

01/2016 - 03/2017

Amol

Developer website and web-application

- Designed and developed .Net computer software web applications.
- Develop website and web applications in MVC architecture for governmental organizations and big companies.
- Worked closely with clients to establish problem specifications and system designs.

EDUCATION

Master of Business AdministrationIslamic Azad University, Science, And Research
Branch

09/2011 - 09/2014

Kermanshah

Ghazvin

Bachelor of Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Qazvin Islamic Azad University

09/2005 – 09/2009

SKILLS

C# HTML & CSS

Python

PHP

C/C++

JavaScript & JS Frameworks (Angular, React, Redux)

Database Technology (SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB)

Java

Git / SVN / TFS

HTTP & REST API / SOAP

PERSONAL PROJECTS

NoonAp (2019) 🗗

PWA (Progressive Web Apps) ecommerce project with ReactJS.

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of Completion: C# Course (2016) 🗹

Sololear

Certificate of Completion: JavaScript Course

(2017) 🗹 Sololearn

Certificate of Completion: PHP Course (2017)

LANGUAGES

Persian

English Germany

0 0 0 0

INTERESTS

Movie

Game

Music